Condition this day and age. A friendly face on every page.
A laugh track floating through the haze. Everything feels safe these days.
The neighbors wave. The children play. The sun shines bright.
The jokes are old. The stories tame. Every episode's the same.
The ending always lets you in
The audience, she credits the role
Who the soul enjoys
But starts to twitch
A portrait on the wall
Moves when no one looks at all
I'll give you an example
One of these channels I speak of
Year ago, they'd be lucky if they get
5 to 10 people in their chat
And most of the time they were just people there to fucking hate on them
So, after they banned those five to ten people, it's just them and their other alt.
That was it.
That was a year ago.
Okay?
That same person now, maybe gets, you know, still nothing but more than one to two people.
Maybe he's lucky now and they'll get ten to twenty-five people, okay?
That's crazy that there's ten to twenty-five people that are actually listening to this
And I've seen some of the chat where they're actually like agreeing with some of these comments and opinions made that are so false
It's ridiculous. I got to wonder if these people are either trolling or they're so fucking drunk
They don't even understand what the fuck they just agreed on or said, you know what I mean? That's just that bad. Okay
Yeah, you can say dude, that's still not a lot. Yeah, well, it's still enough. Okay. It's enough people that still
Worries me. Okay, that 25 people may be thinking what this person's saying is
That's a big problem our country faces right now is media being
You deserve this bitch just very very very wrong information
Okay, and is being used right now by other countries as a way to weaponize themselves to fucking fuck with our political system
And the way we run ourselves as Americans, which is very very very scary and unfortunately
Even our own platforms, okay, and I'm not going to mention names because you probably know why
Are the ones that supposedly or allegedly are allowing these other countries to do that or have
Okay, so I'll give you that safe case number and citation number
to the traffic infraction. Oh
my god. Normal. Oh my god. You
know what I mean. But it's not
okay. How many of you actually
can you know pull up your name
and see even like one or two
cases come up. Okay. And I'm not
talking like I said we're not
perfect but 40. I think that
really does show some type of
pattern. Now here's the thing I
said earlier. The severity of
the cases.
Let me kind of give you a rundown of what those dates is 40 cases of what I saw
I don't think I'd even I thought I think I think I went through all 40 of them
But now that I counted out there's 40 man. I can't believe that I did. I don't think oh your fuck Kate
You're fucked. I'll give you an example
Where we at?
We're right here. You deserve this
Oh, I'm orgasming right now. I'm fucking orgasming. Thank you. God. Thank you God
Here we go
So let's jump back up to the top. So let's start with date range. So the dates on these five these cases filed date as early as
2000 so the year 2000 which she's showing to be 42. I'm 41
so
2000 I graduated in 01. So, you know, I don't know if you know, and it's Iowa
They're a little bit different like they actually show like I don't know. I don't really care
It's all public information. So I don't know what she probably was like maybe 17 or 18 at that age
I don't know what but basically they've got infractions here from year 2000
all the way through that 2025 day orgasm, okay?
And then everywhere in between, all right?
There's not even a period where it was like,
all right, you know, maybe she could deserve this date.
Now, the majority of all these infusions
and the reason I say that are traffic tickets, all right?
And you might say, come on, well, here's the thing.
You can get a ticket, you know,
traffic tickets become pretty serious
when you become a repeat or serial offender, all right?
You can lose your license, which I don't know exactly what's happened, but when you start
reading some of these, it apparently seems like there was times she didn't have a license
or she had one suspended.
She was driving on a suspended license.
So I'm going to assume because I don't think I read or sign anything that that was directly
is, you know, a type of like giving you an example.
This is nothing to do with her.
Let me make that clear.
But how what's another?
What's a way that most people know you can lose your driver's license is being convicted
I didn't see any. Okay, now did I go through all of them? No, but I'm not saying there's any at all. Okay
I have a feeling that this individual if they did lose their license
Which on some of these it looks like they were driving on a what they call a they have an abbreviation for it in Iowa
Isn't that isn't she that it probably most likely had to do with all these traffic infractions now
What's very scary about this is disgusting this person obviously feels that they don't have to follow any laws
and in this case
So many to the point
Shut up, you know, especially on the times that she was found guilty has to say, please
It's like next month next year next week. I mean, it's fucking crazy
We're gonna go just down again, this is not gonna I'll read you the date it comes from but I'm not gonna go in like
fucking from 2000 2001 2002 I already did that that's how I went through it earlier now let me give
you some interesting cases here in addition to the traffic infractions that range anywhere from
driving with no insurance driving when a suspended driver's license driving certain miles over the
speed limit not yielding all sorts of shit all right it's fucking nuts I also saw a couple of
Got my chicken scratch move a car me it may take me a second to read
But there was a possession of a control substance charge
Again, I'm not saying she was found guilty or not guilty. I'm just reading what she was charged. I've been filed
That was back in I think let's see
Okay, I can't read 2014 was the offense date
There was a harassment charge back in 2016. Oh, there was a few cases that it says search warrant
Oh, that was out of 2016. I think I saw another one. Oh
There in 2018
Oh, I want to talk to you
And then you got a new charge that will go over here
Operating a non
What was this one? What's my handwriting there?
I know that's vehicle operating now is that I killed my cats
Well, just let's just read through some of these. I can't read my fucking chicken scratch
Like I said, it's just everywhere and in here in between like I said the severity of it it
No, okay, she's not as bad as like, you know fucking
Trina alright or scheme-ass this shit, you know, but god damn. I mean 40 fucking fucking cases for one state
Every fucking year basically multiple ones every month you're God
I mean and like I said, let's just say these were all fucking traffic infractions. Oh big whoop right fuck. Yeah big whoop
Especially I like I said, I can't I went out going in too much details
I don't know if there's money or you know finds on any of these that are still owed
Which I would hope not especially if this person allegedly is you know simping for somebody and sending a bunch of money
You know, I hope first they're taking care of their own family first when it comes to the finances and second
I hope that they're taking care of their legal shit second off when it comes to finances before they go out simping
But again, not my money. You do it. Whatever you want with your boo. Yes, you cry
But I can't cry, Mary, Mary doesn't love me, Mary doesn't love me, Mary doesn't love
you, bitch, Mary's by now.
People you know has got fucking 40 trafficking, and like I said, they're not all trafficking
What the fuck?
Uh, PayPal me, uh, I don't know if he, I think he, so that's what, thank you for reminding me while we were doing some other shit, I was gonna see if he is actually there, they're investigating him, I don't know if he is locked up, like right now, he did at one point, they arrested him, but I don't know if he's been released, so I can't answer that.
He's been locked up, but I don't know if he's been released and he's waiting in his little apartment till his next hearing or he's in jail
Right now waiting either way jail homeboys facing possibly they're saying on the news
Possibly 10 years of hard labor in the South Korean prison. Don't sound any fun
And all that shits on fucking, you know video evidence, so I don't know
Anyways, let's start reading what some of these are going like I said
I'm just gonna kind of if you want to get all the nitty-gritty you're gonna have to pay 25 bucks not to me
I'm not asking for I'm saying to the Iowa courts online search
But it does tell us the basis of some of these charges here, okay, and the disposition for the most part
So let's just start from the top and work our way down. I'm not gonna go through all 40
I just want to give you an idea. Okay, like I said, I think I went through all of them
And and I wanted to point out some of the other ones that were just different than some of the traffic shit like the possession of drug paraphernalia
You know 18 the harassment charge and 16 possession of control substance and 14. I think that one got dismissed
like i said some of these they may have been dismissed some of these she might have been found guilty
not guilty you can go through all 40 of these tonight if you want and and have fun today's
wednesday night i think tonight's when they have in krakadona you should know about this actually
you're probably gonna hate on me because i'm a i'm a history channel nat geo channel guy yeah i know
Think is when they do the Egyptian stuff the archaeology stuff, which I love and then tomorrow is my favorite because tomorrow is when they do
What is it? What is it? What is it? What is it?
Ray you know, what's up, dude? How are you? Oh shit? I forgot and then I'm also liking right now
Okay, I mean it's like yeah, we get it. We get it. We get it. She's a fucking criminal. She doesn't see if she's above the law
We get that harassment charges not surprising none of this is surprising here. I'm gonna post my link
I actually went over there. She was in my chat trying to participate today.
Who's the clown talking? Oh, he's not a clown. He's a nice guy. He's New Jersey
Courts. He's just, you know, he gets to the bottom of things, you know, a little bit
different from some of the people you might be. He's in the community, but I
think New Jersey Courts is a good guy, you know.
Um, wow. Okay. So I will always say person is in there. I said, okay, person. He's blocking me. Yeah.
Not tell me in person what to do. I thought person was been that beat his mod. Oh, but, oh, the best friends now, though.
Oh, the best friends now, right? Oh, and then who said, someone said, oh, healer, you look better than psyche any day.
Have you seen this one? I mean, I think she's on the thumbnail. I know I'm not perfect right now.
I do have a little bit of a
Narrow forehead. I don't know. It's not really balding. Is that really balding? I don't know. I don't have a gray hair in my head
But okay, we can take a look what she looks like. She is actually this is just from her show
This is not doxing. This is just
Neither is what I just showed. I didn't even show her last thing. It's just a Kate Ellen
I guess that's her name. This is what she looks like. I'm gonna see what she really looks like. She looks like this
That's why she probably got mad because
Okay, well, I don't know but that's what she looks like
She looks like, she looks like the Jolly Green Giants
in this carriage.
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, she's just disgusting.
That's what she looks like.
That's probably the, that's generous.
That's a nice picture of her.
It's a really nice picture of her.
Oh, go back and forth.
Go run and tell her what I'm saying.
Oh, you little bitches.
Some of you are little bitches.
That's okay.
It's okay.
People that are here are good people, most of them.
Some of them are just these ass lickers.
They want to be in the chat.
They, I mean, they think they're something.
There besides. Oh, she says right there. She's trans and swollen. Yeah, I wouldn't be surprised if she had a penis
But I'd be surprised. Oh, it comes out Kate has a penis. I mean, I wasn't surprised about a hammer
Hammer's boob deflated. Yeah, if she's not a man, she's like the ugliest woman I've ever seen but it's okay
I mean, I'm not trying to put people down, but is she deserves it actually? Okay, but that's just what she looks like
Okay
Yeah
Sick. She said, oh, well, she said, oh, show, show my cats. I showed Lenore today
They're asking they're saying oh Rudy. Um, it was you know, it's not Alex. That's Kate the turtle
They look kind of similar, but no, it's not Alex. Yeah. Hey, right, you know, right, you know, who are so who are you, huh?
I know you're a winner. I know you. I'm just gonna now we need flashbacks
You know you sound like a cool guy
I don't know. I mean, I'm sure I think a lot of people are just running over there
I didn't have a great chance today with like a hundred people
I but I guess other people are on right now we can like let me see if I can find it's in her
She's talking about me. Let me see if that's any of that's still up. Hold on a sec
Let me just go to this this this fat cunts page one second. Okay. Um, I
Guess I'll have to share my full screen. Yeah, I'm glad I got a laugh. Yeah, it's Kate the turtle. Yeah, it's not that's a yeah
Alex is a little bit darker. Alex is a little bit darker skin
Just as ugly, but yeah, I mean if you're talking about the heart. Yeah
No soul no heart no love
I mean, I feel bad in a way almost these are very damaged damaged women
Very damaged women. I mean, it's like it maybe you know, yeah
So I'll board the hate train, the Kate train, you know, Kate and hate, but you know, that's if it's funny that rhymes, okay?
Let me just have a look. Okay. So let me see. I'll just go to her chat right now. I when I came in earlier
I was trying to be cordial
She decided to yell at me and so was Kate show 420. I'm so happy. I found that Docs though. I think I'm so happy
Next I gotta get Christine's. Oh my god. It's so great. These are all people that are just attacking me, right?
I'm gonna pause her show and I'm saying if everyone watching this right now made a contribution
We've reached our goal in seconds, but I know not everyone can give right now
So if you care about taking say fine, okay?
Here we go. I just have a pause. I have a pause. I'm gonna do a full screen. Yeah, it's Kate the turtle
Isn't that crazy? Isn't that crazy? That's what that's what she looks like
That's what she really looks like guys. You're you're you're hero Kate your hero Kate
Here we go. Let's just look at her chat. Let's see what the chat is saying in there. Here we go.
I know. Isn't she disgusting? She's just vulgar. Okay, here we go. Let's have a look at her chat.
Kate the turtle. Wow. Why are you so mean to me? I'm actually not a bad person that I will defend myself.
Okay, so let me go to the top of it. Oh, let's see who's in there. Okay, so here's in there.
Okay, hi William. Hi William because you see this William glory holes in there. Hi Kate. Hi Amber AJJ person
I got all my comments are deleted
But let me see there you go person show us Rudy. We miss him. Please. That's Josie Grossi
And then it says 988 count his batteries giving the suicide hotline number B people is laughing
Well said Kate. Okay, can his bathroom is an animal abuser
Then it says pack yourself up psyche. That's g6. He will be banned next time. Hey Moshe. How are you?
No, no, no, never mind. He said hate psyche. Okay, never mind. Go ahead. Go to fucking hell Moshe on King David
Hey, I know King David. He doesn't like you. He says stop using his name
Oh, you mean he let his old ass ancient cat out and hasn't it come back the orange one or it's dead like tricks
Rudy definitely passed away 100% that's some good tea Rudy never went out ever well on top of that cat looking like it had
Cancer, it's coyote season. He said Lenora has been here the entire time. So why isn't?
It hanging out around him.
The orange cat looked like it was losing weight a lot
and dying of cancer.
Guess you didn't see Lenore today.
That's what I, this is me,
it's like he's nine years old, that was me.
Cry about it.
And Josie says he was old.
It's only, it's the only cat death
that actually makes sense.
He couldn't hide it.
So he neglected an old cat.
Next alt.
So the cat left to die.
You couldn't take it to get euthanized.
He did show Lenore, but not Rudy.
And he yelled at me for asking so they don't suffer.
Taking a cat to the vet means doing something for himself, can't even buy a litter box or
flea medication, and needs internet strangers to do it. No, Psyche can't get off the couch,
but has to steal from the liquor store, but he can't do anything for his senior cat.
Laughing. His address is out, call Animal Control. He walks by Animal Control every morning to steal
coffee. Rui was meowing a lot, and he never meowed. It was clear something was wrong,
but he couldn't take his cat there. Yeah, he was meowing just to tell him.
Psyche steals so you mean they were false Kate Kate tell me that's Christine and the thumb Christine's car in the thumbnail
Well, no one likes Christine. Okay. I mean wild. Okay, so I guess they the car that allows people that's Christine
Yeah, okay. Okay. I guess that was it. Um, okay, so you can see how they talk
That's this horrible horrible lady bathroom person so sick
so sick
Kate has their attainment value unless she's crashing out get on the panel. Yeah, come on. No, I I tried I tried and she yelled at me
She said I'm not welcome over there. So it's okay. I mean I let her in my chat
I would have let her in my panel
But hey, but you know what you come on my panel right now. You're by the way, this is our picture right there
So come on up guys. You're scared. You're scared of Kate that she'll eat you.
Okay, I actually have a video called Big Back Kate and I will be finding that video.
You can go to ColtCodex.me. You can find every episode of my show that I've ever done. You can find the transcripts.
I actually made the transcripts all public at this point. They're all all all public. Okay?
Everyone can search the transcripts now, okay?
Here's Kolkutik, stop me.
I will, let's look up Kate the Turtle right here, okay?
I'm gonna look up Big Back Kate video.
One second, let me just look up a Big Back Kate.
Big Back Kate, Big Back Kate.
Let's find that video, Big Back Kate.
This is actually, some people thought it was Shrek 3.
Big Back Kate.
This is the true story of Kate
and a little person named Bear Bear.
Now Bear Bear, he used Kate.
And he laughs about it.
Okay.
BigBatKate, I found the episode, guys.
I found it, 16 minutes.
And here's the episode.
Wow, I found it, 16 minutes?
Is this the, oh, I found the video.
Guys, I love my codecs.
Search BigBatKate, you'll find it.
Oh my God.
So good, so good.
Here, I'm sharing.
You want to see it when they entertained. I actually made a good good AI video. You can see you can see big back hate, right?
Ready for it. Hey, are you ready for it? You know the Taylor Swift says
You swamp folk, your goblins, trolls, and geese.
I'll tell you a big back Kate, whose backside had no seats.
She lived beside a muddy bog in her castle made of crates.
Where she hosts the talk shows every night for nosy, miserable mates.
A big back Kate, big back Kate.
The old gress queen of gossip and hate.
She'd call folks laughing cows all day,
Moo-moo cake, moo-moo cake
The biggest laughing cow in the state
It fell hard for a little bear bearer giant dressed in black
A pimp so smooth he could sell snow to a penguin in a shack
His hat was made of raven feathers, his boots were crocodile
He'd wink at every village girl from a quarter of a mile
didn't care for Kate's romantic schemes.
He mostly liked her giant back for transportation needs.
Oh, big back Kate, big back Kate.
The troll expressed her fate.
She'd carry bare bare 50 miles while he counted cash
in practice miles.
Take me north, Bear Bear would say
She'd run through mud and rain
Take me south, take me east
Then she'd do it all again
She hauled him over mountains
Across valleys, lakes, and creeks
Wally sat upon her shoulders
Eating twelve rotisserie freaks
Nobody knows what a rotisserie freak is
And frankly, that's okay
The village scholar studded one and retired the next day.
Kate gave him gold, Kate gave him gems, Kate gave him forty cows.
Kate gave him an enchanted spoon that only complimented ours.
She bought him seven haunted wagons, she bought him thirteen foxes.
She bought him socks for all his socks and socks for those socks socks.
Kay, financial disaster and carnage
She spent so much on little bear
Bear the kingdom, swift to seashells
Out of despair
Each night she'd host her famous show
The Business, isn't it yours?
Where trolls discuss their neighbors' curtains
Fences, roofs and doors
They'd analyze a cabbage patch
They'd investigate a shoe
They once debated 17 weeks
About a squirrel named Stu
One troll asked who is still nobody knew
But that did not stop season two
Ain't what shoud you-
laughing cows at every guess she'd meet. Then she'd accidentally catch herself in a mirror on the
street. She'd gasp and shock, she'd faint outright, she'd yell, who is that beast? The mirror answered,
ma'am, that's you. And attendance sharply decreased. One day, Bear Bear finally left upon a disco
The Yak wore roller skates and pearls and never once looked back.
Kate cried tear so huge and thick they flooded.
Free fishermen got trapped inside a sentimental lawn.
A wizard tried to help her heal.
She ate the wizard's hat.
Nobody knows why she did that, actually.
That's pretty on brand for Kate.
Legend still circulates. She never won bear bears heart, but she hauled him everywhere from the start
She called folks cows. She spread the tea. She sponsored swirl inquiries, and if you hear a distant moon
Across the moonlit lake
That's probably not a cow at all
It's the ghostly echo of big back Kate move. I made my point
It's called a W
So it's called a double
And it'll be on rumble tomorrow. I'm leading the stream
So that fat cunt doesn't strike it, but have a good night
That's where you Kate me kissy me kissy poo. Yeah fucking fat cunt as bad. I hope you fuck it